<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jonathan Mainguy</title>
    <link>https://jmainguy.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jonathan Mainguy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 08:39:20 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jmainguy.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mifare Ultralight Ev1 48</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/posts/mifare-ultralight-ev1-48/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 08:39:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/posts/mifare-ultralight-ev1-48/</guid>
      <description>We went on vacation to our condo in Myrtle Beach this week. The water was warm, and the fireworks went all night every day. The kids seemed to have a good time, my sister and parents also came with us which was a nice treat.
It appears one of our previous renters must have placed their outdoor rusty beach chair on our carpet and setup for a bit, so there is now a rust stain on the carpet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Babo Is Dead Long Live Babo</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/posts/babo-is-dead-long-live-babo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 09:46:50 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/posts/babo-is-dead-long-live-babo/</guid>
      <description>It is the end of an era, today I have shut off the &amp;ldquo;master&amp;rdquo; server for baboviolent 2, that people could connect to and see other babo servers to play on. BV2 was a really fun top down shooting game where the characters were balls that rolled around. I enjoyed playing it as much as I enjoyed hosting it in the latter years. I have very fond memories of playing on =TM= with Size, Deathreay and the rest, as well as (tb) with Allen and the gang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid Data as of 9-29-2021</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/posts/covid-data-9-29-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 13:33:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/posts/covid-data-9-29-2021/</guid>
      <description>I recently created a stock price operator for Kubernetes, to gather the current price of stock for a list of tickers the user defines. Doing so, I learned the same API I was using for the stock, also had some Covid-19 data in it as well.
The code was pretty quick to work out thanks to the great API docs and examples.
package main import ( &amp;#34;context&amp;#34; &amp;#34;fmt&amp;#34; finnhub &amp;#34;github.com/Finnhub-Stock-API/finnhub-go/v2&amp;#34; ) func main() { cfg := finnhub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ugly Drum Smoker</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/posts/ugly-drum-smoker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 09:51:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/posts/ugly-drum-smoker/</guid>
      <description>My old horizontal barrel grill was falling apart, so I set out to replace it. After looking at Big Green Egg and Kamodo Joe reviews they seemed awesome, but the price was crazy and I didn&amp;rsquo;t want to be out 2k if I knocked it over on accident. (its porcelain, its gonna shatter if tipped over.)
I also enjoy DIY and spending $2,000 on a smoker seemed to be at odds with smoking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to setup travis-ci with goreleaser for automated binary golang releases</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/how-to-setup-travis-ci-with-goreleaser-for-automated-binary-golang-releases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 13:15:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/how-to-setup-travis-ci-with-goreleaser-for-automated-binary-golang-releases/</guid>
      <description>I have been enjoying writing golang applications for a few years now, and I naively assumed other people who wanted to use them could easily build the apps with instructions I provided easy enough.
I discovered that the differences between operating systems is enough that compiling the applications can be burdensome for others. My buddy @slm (hes kind of a big deal) mentioned I should check out goreleaser and I am glad I did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sweet pawn shop find</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/sweet-pawn-shop-find/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2017 19:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/sweet-pawn-shop-find/</guid>
      <description>I have recently started hobbying with pawn shop guitars, found this LTD a few months ago for $100, noticed it had Seymour Duncans humbucking pickups installed. The guitar was going for $300 new, but I see it now on amazon for $245. My rule of thumb is used gear is worth about 50% of new price, so $100 is already a good deal, add on upgraded pickups and I jumped at the deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The flag, the national anthem, and what they mean to me.</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/the-flag-the-national-anthem-and-what-they-mean-to-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 15:07:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/the-flag-the-national-anthem-and-what-they-mean-to-me/</guid>
      <description>My earliest memory of reverence for the flag, was seeing it flying on a huge pole in front of my Grandpa’s house. We would go see him once a year for thanksgiving and my cousins would come as well, was always a really good time. pulling up and seeing that flag meant we had arrived from the long 12 hour trip (a lifetime for a van full of kids and tiger electronic handheld games).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old School Football review – 1991 #1 Florida State vs Tulane</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/old-school-football-review-1991-1-florida-state-vs-tulane/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 04:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/old-school-football-review-1991-1-florida-state-vs-tulane/</guid>
      <description>FSU vs Tulane
Casey Weldon, and Amp Lee tear up the Tulane Defense all game, doing anything they want. 31 points before getting pulled at the end of the third.
Brad Johnson comes in at the beginning of the 4th. A pick bounces off a receiver and into the hands of a defender, not the QB’s fault. Next drive Brad completes a TD pass to one of the tight ends. Marking 4 TE touchdowns in this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I wrote a sms survey application</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/i-wrote-a-sms-survey-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 18:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/i-wrote-a-sms-survey-application/</guid>
      <description>My pastor was looking for a sms survey service, requirements: A number to give out, a way to gather the responses, easy to use, cheap as possible. Googling turned up a few results with no clear pricing and salesmen, one I found was about $50 a month. Since I work at a telephone company, I decided just to make one using our API.
I am calling the application “Survey Hail”, as its a survey service, and a play of words on the pastors name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old School Football review – 1991 Pigskin Classic #1 Florida State vs #19 BYU</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/old-school-football-review-1991-pigskin-classic-1-florida-state-vs-19-byu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/old-school-football-review-1991-pigskin-classic-1-florida-state-vs-19-byu/</guid>
      <description>I recently started watching old school football games, so I figured I would write a review while I am at it. I love the Noles, so I will be watching their games.
The year is 1991, FSU is preseason ranked #1 in the nation, and has for some reason, opted to open the year at a “neutral” site in Anaheim California, Disneyland, against the Heisman trophy winner, Ty Detmer lead #19 BYU Cougars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I wrote a gotosleep daemon</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/i-wrote-a-gotosleep-daemon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 19:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/i-wrote-a-gotosleep-daemon/</guid>
      <description>I watch youtube / twitch at night to go to sleep to. I am too lazy to open a command line and say shutdown in 120 minutes or so. So instead I wrote a tool, which reads a config, and shuts down at the time specified every night.
https://github.com/Jmainguy/gotosleep
Currently only works on Linux as that’s what I use, and I doubt anybody else will use this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrambled egg and bacon on toasted potato bread sammitch</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/scrambled-egg-and-bacon-on-toasted-potato-bread-sammitch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2017 00:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/scrambled-egg-and-bacon-on-toasted-potato-bread-sammitch/</guid>
      <description>Stole most of the recipe from http://allrecipes.com/recipe/239871/toms-scrambled-egg-sandwich/. Fry 3 strips of bacon, leave grease in pan, set cooked bacon aside. put two pieces of bread in toaster. Mix 2 eggs, a little more than a splash of milk, handful of shredded cheddar cheese, salt, and old bay in a bowl until it all comes together. pour into frying pan ontop of the grease and leave it alone. Once its done cooking on one side try and and flip it, fail and settle some of it shredding, attempt to cook on other side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mothers day Wings</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/mothers-day-wings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2017 23:34:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/mothers-day-wings/</guid>
      <description>Did pancakes, bacon, cinnamon rolls, and mimosas’s for brunch, Leah cooked it all up, it was too delicious to take pictures of. Ended up doing grilled wings for dinner, shoulda cooked 4-5 more but they were great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I got DK64 working again</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/i-got-dk64-working-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2017 17:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/i-got-dk64-working-again/</guid>
      <description>About 16 years ago a low life scum bag stole my Expansion Card for the N64. This was needed for DK64 to work, so since then I have not been able to play. I finally bit the bullet and purchased an expansion card on ebay (about $20 USD) and it booted right up. Now to play through it from scratch =)
Love that red color Japanese words. Sitting in its new home Booted up no problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bacon Wrapped, Old Bay Seasoned, Ribeye Burgers, dressed with East Carolina Vinegar based BBQ sauce</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/bacon-wrapped-old-bay-seasoned-ribeye-burgers-dressed-with-east-carolina-vinegar-based-bbq-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2017 23:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/bacon-wrapped-old-bay-seasoned-ribeye-burgers-dressed-with-east-carolina-vinegar-based-bbq-sauce/</guid>
      <description>Leah said it was burger night, so might as well do it right. Bought a ribeye steak, then sliced it up and cut off the excess fat and tissue (leave some of the fat, otherwise you get a dry burger). Formed patties, seasoned it with salt and old bay. Wrap it with bacon. Place on grill.
Once its nearly done, grill your buns and top burgers with cheese. Leave burgers in until the cheese is molten, and dripping into the fire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I wrote https://soh.re from scratch go check it out</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/i-wrote-httpssoh-re-from-scratch-go-check-it-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 17:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/i-wrote-httpssoh-re-from-scratch-go-check-it-out/</guid>
      <description>I have always wanted a interactive website that looks like a Linux shell. When @ChrisShort tweeted about GoTTY, I knew I had the essential piece I was missing.
I wanted each page reload to bring a fresh copy of the site (because people are mean and will wreck the shell they are in on purpose, I know I would). I wanted it to be secure (I do not want people ddosing others, or bringing down my infra), and I wanted to have a few fun things for them to do (like play crawl, or chat on IRC).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Got the PizzaKettle working on the third try</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/got-the-pizzakettle-working-on-the-third-try/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2017 23:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/got-the-pizzakettle-working-on-the-third-try/</guid>
      <description>First two were pretty meh, but attempt number #3 came out tonight. Things I did different this time, using my own pizza pan instead of the included one, kept the pizza stone in the entire time so the stone itself was hot and ready when the pizza was placed. Lots of wood to keep the temp as high as I can get it (gauge only goes to 700, so above that).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBQ Day was a success</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/bbq-day-was-a-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 00:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/bbq-day-was-a-success/</guid>
      <description>Did a BBQ day, our good friends Dustin and Liz came to help eat it all. Wings, Ribs, and slow cooked pulled pork. It was great.
Aux grill, to get coals hot enough to transfer to pig grill Fan to feed the fires the oxygen it craves. Oxygen entry point, careful its hot. 250 degrees, hard work trying to keep it consistent. mmmm delicious smoke Pork and Ribs ready to come off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A full morning</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/a-full-morning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 15:26:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/a-full-morning/</guid>
      <description>Went to the store for some drip pans, put the pork on the bbq, made flapjacks. Mmmm delicious flapjacks.
6 pounds, bone in. Cook for 6ish hours at 250, Flapjacks and Sausage on the griddle
Looking forward to tonight, gonna do some wings and ribs as well.
Ribs marinating East Carolina Sauce ready to go</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I had lunch today and bought some cigar boxes</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/i-had-lunch-today-and-bought-some-cigar-boxes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 17:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/i-had-lunch-today-and-bought-some-cigar-boxes/</guid>
      <description>Barrett asked for pictures from Lunch, so here they are. He is a jerk and should come to lunch next time.
They make some great food here. I got the buffalo chicken wrap today. My table for today, all by my lonesome. At the smoke shop grabbing boxes, really nice inside. Sweet moose. Classic size box, the best for making guitars. Nice looking wood. Cool latch What I made my first guitar out of, good box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My minecraft business is dead</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/my-minecraft-business-is-dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 23:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/my-minecraft-business-is-dead/</guid>
      <description>I started a minecraft business to help pay for hosting my own minecraft server. It blew up and I ended up getting alot of customers really quick. I stopped marketing to get new clients about 2-3 years ago and when I checked today the last of my word of mouth people stopped paying about 3 months ago. So I am cancelling my whmcs license and redirecting the website to the open source code the business generated (which I am also doing a poor job of maintaining).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I made a guitar hanger</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/i-made-a-guitar-hanger/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 03:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/i-made-a-guitar-hanger/</guid>
      <description>I need more guitar hangers, and they cost $10 a pop from amazon, also I can only place them on studs, which limits where I can place them. The solution was a guitar hanger which ended up costing about the same ($23 for wood board, $10 for all hangers, $7 for stain). I think it looks great though.
So nice
5x hangers
http://www.homedepot.com/p/Everbilt-Heavy-Duty-Screw-In-Tool-Hanger-24255/205020421
1x oak board
Go to home depot lumber section and pick one out</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cooked some Barbacoa</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/cooked-some-barbacoa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 01:14:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/cooked-some-barbacoa/</guid>
      <description>Made some Barbacoa for burrito’s tonight, really turned out great. You sear some chuck roast, mix a bunch of other stuff in a blender, then pour over the beef in a slow cooker, cook up for 6 hours, shred, enjoy. Michael and Leah made some cilantro lime rice and black beans to go with it.
The delicious shredded barbacoa in the slow cooker. Cilantro lime rice. All ready to be rolled up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I made some burgers</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/i-made-some-burgers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 03:26:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/i-made-some-burgers/</guid>
      <description>I decided to make some burgers for dinner. Went to the store and got boneless chuck eye steak, some chips, potato bread, and soda.
Got home and cut up the chuck into small enough chunks to form a patty.
Only used one of these and wrapped the rest. Made two patties easy. Nice and fatty.
Cooked the bacon first, so I could add it to the burger later, and hopefully get some grease in the pan for the burgers to cook in (turkey bacon let me down)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ho made pizza night</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/ho-made-pizza-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 00:24:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/ho-made-pizza-night/</guid>
      <description>I enjoy pizza, so I decided to make some. Made the dough yesterday, let it sit overnight in the fridge, then topped and baked tonight. Delicious
Followed this Recipe for the dough. Could not find 00 flour so I used bread flour instead, will have to buy some 00 online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I handmade a guitar</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/i-handmade-a-guitar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 01:17:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/i-handmade-a-guitar/</guid>
      <description>Finally wrapped up my big guitar project. Finished the guitar yesterday and learned how to play it correctly today (have to use a slide or it wont sound right). Pretty happy with how it turned out.
Metal rod for nut. Straight cut headstock. Wood burned fret markers made by hand. Metal rod again for the bridge. Will clean up these sound holes later this week. Piezo jack pickup.
I have no idea why my phone recorded this vertically, I placed it horizontally and all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I made some Audio cables</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/i-made-some-audio-cables/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 02:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/i-made-some-audio-cables/</guid>
      <description>I needed a 3.5mm to 3.5mm to connect my digital to audio connect (dac) to my headphone amp (which makes headphones sound better). So I spent alot of time last week and made one.
love that color. Wont get it confused with other peoples cords ever.
Then today I spent about 6 hours making another cord. This one was to connect my Electronic Drum kit to the mixer at church. I needed a 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I built a workbench</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/i-built-a-workbench/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2016 19:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/i-built-a-workbench/</guid>
      <description>I needed a workbench to start on my new hobbies and projects. So I went ahead and built one. I needed a bench that could fold up as the Wife and I both park inside the garage and refuse to give that up. I followed the tutorial at http://www.remodelaholic.com/diy-portable-workbench-folding-table/. The shopping cart of the stuff I bought. https://etherpad.soh.re/p/workbench. I got the plywood cut at home depot and they did a great job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Openshift online is cool if you play by the rules</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/openshift-online-is-cool-if-you-play-by-the-rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2016 02:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/openshift-online-is-cool-if-you-play-by-the-rules/</guid>
      <description>So my good buddy Andrew Butcher @akbutcher took pity on me and pointed me in the right direction. After rebuilding the docker container on the assumption that any random user could be running it, it worked like a charm. See the updated code at https://github.com/Jmainguy/docker_images/tree/master/etherpad and launch your own openshift-online version of etherpad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You can’t push a docker image to Openshift and just run it</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/you-cant-push-a-docker-image-to-openshift-and-just-run-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2016 21:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/you-cant-push-a-docker-image-to-openshift-and-just-run-it/</guid>
      <description>So I just finished wasting 3 hours of my life trying to get a docker image to run on Redhats PAAS openshift online, and I failed. In short, you can push a docker image to openshift, but it ignores most of the directives in the Dockerfile and rewrites them as it pleases. It then runs the image as any user it wants, and you cant change that, because you are not a open shift admin, on account of using their PAAS instead of running it yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seth’s Funeral – Saturday at 11am in Garner, NC</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/seths-funeral-saturday-at-11am-in-garner-nc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 13:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/seths-funeral-saturday-at-11am-in-garner-nc/</guid>
      <description>Funeral services will be held on Saturday April 30th at 11:00am at Triangle Baptist Church. The address is 9713 Old Stage Rd, Raleigh, NC 27603.
Following the service, a reception will be held at Lake Benson park located 921 Buffaloe Rd, Garner, NC 27529.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seth Mainguy has passed</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/seth-mainguy-has-passed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2016 00:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/seth-mainguy-has-passed/</guid>
      <description>Today Seth passed away. 8/20/14 – 4/23/16</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The original pokemon is pretty bad</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/the-original-pokemon-is-pretty-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2016 20:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/the-original-pokemon-is-pretty-bad/</guid>
      <description>Got nostalgic, installed retro-pi on my raspberry pi and been playing Pokemon Red on it. It is not as good as I remembered it. First, despite being for the Game Boy Color, its not in color. WTF? Second, you cannot bind a key to an item or move, like say I want select to be the bicycle, or select to be the cut move to cut down bushes, nope. Third, Pokebox’s get full?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My son has Leukemia</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/my-son-has-leukemia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2015 20:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/my-son-has-leukemia/</guid>
      <description>At Seth’s one year checkup we found a blood anomaly, after talking to a specialist in Chapel Hill, it turned out to be AML Leukemia.
So far we have completed two 30 day rounds of inpatient hospital care, with another 2 more to go. This is typically 10 days of chemotherapy followed by 20 days of waiting for you immune system to recover, and then you get about a week to 10 days at home before you start the next round.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Cyanogenmod 12.1 on Galaxy S3</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/install-cyanogenmod-12-1-on-galaxy-s3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2015 20:27:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/install-cyanogenmod-12-1-on-galaxy-s3/</guid>
      <description>Phone broke over the weekend, now I get to use the wife’s old S3 to replace my S3, I hope it can do the job =). I insist on using cyanogenmod on my phones as its an awesome OS. This is how I installed it today from my Fedora 22 laptop.
Install needed tools on Laptop a. dnf install android-tools heimdall
Download gapps, cyanogenmod, and CWM a. http://download2.clockworkmod.com/recoveries/recovery-clockwork-6.0.4.5-d2spr.img
b. https://download.cyanogenmod.org/get/jenkins/121988/cm-12.1-20150817-NIGHTLY-d2spr.zip</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chasing the cheese truck #AmericanMeltdown</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/chasing-the-cheese-truck-americanmeltdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 20:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/chasing-the-cheese-truck-americanmeltdown/</guid>
      <description>Today I was lucky enough to be able to chase the cheese truck. If you work at a cool place, they will have the cheese truck come to your place around lunch time. Redhat did that for us almost a year ago, and I got hooked on #AmericanMeltdown. Their Buffalo Blitz sandwich is phenomenal. It is basically a grilled cheese with buffalo chicken in the middle. I get the horseradish chips and the best soda in the world to go along with it, good times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sinatrarb-virt-manager</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/sinatrarb-virt-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2015 03:52:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/sinatrarb-virt-manager/</guid>
      <description>A client asked me to write him a web app, which would let him stop/start/restart his VM’s he hosts via libvirt. This is the initial implementation to answer his request.
I next need to add logins for this to be useful at all, but its neat how easy sinatrarb makes creating a web app.
https://github.com/Jmainguy/sinatrarb-virt-manager is the code
http://phy01.standouthost.com:8080/ is the demo, go nuts.
I am basically just capturing the action requested from the browser, and passing it to bash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Root your host in 2 easy steps with Docker</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/root-your-host-in-2-easy-steps-with-docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2015 03:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/root-your-host-in-2-easy-steps-with-docker/</guid>
      <description>So lets assume jmainguy is a user on your system, and he asks to be added to the docker group so he can spin up docker containers and such, seems like a fairly reasonable request. You add him to the docker group.
jmainguy then complains that he cant share data among-st his containers via -v volume mounting, selinux is stopping him. He wanted to mount some gluster storage shared between the containers, a fairly reasonable request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>deleting files with sinatrarb</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/deleting-files-with-sinatrarb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 14:23:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/deleting-files-with-sinatrarb/</guid>
      <description>With sinatrarb you can create a quick web app in ruby very easily, their documentation is great.
http://www.sinatrarb.com/intro.html
One thing you can do, is send a file, like say a tar file.
send_file “certs/#{filename}/#{filename}.tar”, :filename =&amp;gt; “#{filename}.tar”
I was hosting this on openshift which has a hard drive limitation of 1gb, so I needed to cleanup after each send. Turns out, you cannot simply place FileUtils.rm_rf(‘directorypath/name’) after send_file to do the job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fuck Lenovo and their T540P</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/fuck-lenovo-and-their-t540p/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2014 01:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/fuck-lenovo-and-their-t540p/</guid>
      <description>Seriously, fuck them and every fucking engineer and designer they have on staff that gave this model a thumbs up.
Pros:
beast cpu, 8 cores of 2.7ghz i7
beast ram, 16 fucking gigs of ram
beast screen, its fucking crazy high def.
Whats not to love?
Cons:
The fucking keyboard is non standard, and has a fucking function button where the control button should be. So all the fucking muscle memmory you built up over the years wont work on this device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delete email template duplicates from WHMCS</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/delete-email-template-duplicates-from-whmcs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 03:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/delete-email-template-duplicates-from-whmcs/</guid>
      <description>After upgrading WHMCS this weekend I noticed I had duplicate email templates. I used the following sql to delete them.
CREATE TABLE new_table AS
SELECT * FROM tblemailtemplates WHERE 1 GROUP BY name;
drop table tblemailtemplates;
RENAME TABLE new_table TO tblemailtemplates;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lynchburg for the weekend</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/lynchburg-for-the-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2013 21:13:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/lynchburg-for-the-weekend/</guid>
      <description>Headed to Lynchburg for the weekend. Hit me up if you want to hang out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miami Dolphins #1</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/miami-dolphins-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2013 23:37:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/miami-dolphins-1/</guid>
      <description>I am pysched for tonights game, the first step towards our dominance of the AFC East. However Let me say a few things about our team.
Ryan Tannehill is a mediocre wide receiver, his backup is a winner, not a Dan Marino but the best QB we have is Matt Moore, he should be starting.
Jeff Ireland is an idiot, who makes idiotic choices. We need him gone yesterday. Please please please, fire this man.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blake hotel survey</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/blake-hotel-survey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2013 21:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/blake-hotel-survey/</guid>
      <description>The Blake hotel in Charlotte is awful, but they asked me to fill out a survey to get a grip on my experience. Here it is, [ Warning curse words]
There is nowhere to idle car while checking in. Doorman disappeared when they saw us pull up.
Website site WiFi, once checked in you find out it is $9 a day. This is free at every hotel I have ever stayed at, or choose to stay at again in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moral Dilemma</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/moral-dilemma/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 17:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/moral-dilemma/</guid>
      <description>My moral dilemma for the day made me realize I might be more nerdy then I thought I was. Do I play Dungeons and Dragons tonight, or go to the Triangle linux user group meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Got him</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/got-him/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2013 00:46:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/got-him/</guid>
      <description>We got the terrorist alive, go America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working from home today</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/working-from-home-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 14:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/working-from-home-today/</guid>
      <description>My Office in the bedroom
Hallway between Bedroom and Leah’s office
Leah’s unpacked office with temp desk until real one is procured.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All moved in</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/all-moved-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 02:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/all-moved-in/</guid>
      <description>The move took about 3 hours today. Nile and Chris helping made a huge job easy. Definitely worn out now but enjoying the media room. The couch is comfy, fights are good to watch and the girls are getting me pizza. I am a happy man</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old Glory</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/old-glory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2013 16:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/old-glory/</guid>
      <description>The new house came with a flag pole and flag, reminds me of Grandpa Creel</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Officially Homeowners</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/officially-homeowners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Feb 2013 00:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/officially-homeowners/</guid>
      <description>Finally signed all the papers and got the Keys. Leah and I are now officially homeowners / Slaves to the bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The house has a Carport</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/the-house-has-a-carport/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2012 13:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/the-house-has-a-carport/</guid>
      <description>Picture of the beast carport where I will be setting up a basketball hoop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Under Contract</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/under-contract/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 17:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/under-contract/</guid>
      <description>The sellers have agreed to all terms and we have a signed contract. Now the mad rush to get inspection and appraisal, its a new house though, not expecting any issues. Very excited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Countering Counter</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/countering-counter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 16:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/countering-counter/</guid>
      <description>Seller came back with a counter, we just finished submitting our counter to said counter. Negotiating is going good, excited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linked to Twitter</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/linked-to-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 03:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/linked-to-twitter/</guid>
      <description>And now Jmainguy.com is linked to Twitter and Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>And back to the original plugin</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/and-back-to-the-original-plugin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 23:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/and-back-to-the-original-plugin/</guid>
      <description>So apparently Facebook just ignores and I have to use periods. This should look good if I am correct, means my posts have to look like sentences and stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Mono 3.0.1 on Centos Linux 6.3</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/installing-mono-3-0-1-on-centos-linux-6-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 22:53:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/installing-mono-3-0-1-on-centos-linux-6-3/</guid>
      <description>So you want to run windows .exe’s on your shiny Linux server, time to catch mono.
To install mono first install your dependencies.
Congrats, you now have Mono installed and can run some Windows .exe’s such as Terraria or Minecraft Classic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buying a House</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/buying-a-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2012 18:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/buying-a-house/</guid>
      <description>Our negotiations with the first house fell through, the owner was not living in reality and thought his house was worth tax value. However we really love the house we saw yesterday and placed a bid on that one, it has everything we are looking for and wont need any work to move in. Lord clearly did not want us to have the last house for a reason. Excited!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing Integration with Facebook</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/testing-integration-with-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2012 03:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/testing-integration-with-facebook/</guid>
      <description>I rejoined facebook to boost the ol SEO. This is a test to see if integation with facebook is working.
So to get your website to post to Facebook, you have to create a dev account with Facebook. They require you to add a valid call phone or credit card, seems pretty anoying. After that you create a app (click a few buttons no coding needed) and get the api code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Misery</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/misery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2012 15:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/misery/</guid>
      <description>Click on image for larger size. Created using http://stripgenerator.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hit and Run</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/hit-and-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2012 13:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/hit-and-run/</guid>
      <description>Friday night my baby sister went to my cousins a few miles away to babysit for the night. She comes home frantic around 11pm and explains some jerk side swiped her car on her way home. This guy gets out to check and make sure she is ok, then jumps in his car and leaves. If I ever find this guy you can imagine I will have a few choice words for the kind of scumbag that he is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TS3 Non Profit License</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/ts3-non-profit-license/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2012 04:38:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/ts3-non-profit-license/</guid>
      <description>The community Teamspeak server has been full lately and we do not want anyone to miss out on the action. Tonight we applied for a Non profit license which will enable us to host up to 512 members over 10 private servers (So we will never be full again =). Cross your fingers.
[Update] Teamspeak has granted the license, we can host up to 512 slots now. We had some issues with the VPS provider in Kansas and have moved the server to California with BuyVM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smallgrits Macbook</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/smallgrits-macbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 18:07:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/smallgrits-macbook/</guid>
      <description>Maggie moved in with us a few weeks ago to attend NC State. Her 2 year old Macbook Pro stopped booting up a few days later. I was able to run a diagnostic on the pc and discovered one of the Ram cards was giving an error. After removing the offending ram the issue persisted. Maggie took the pc to the mac-store for the “Genius’s” to take a look. They convinced her it was a bad hard drive and could fix it for $200.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturday, Time to do stuff I don’t enjoy</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/saturday-time-to-do-stuff-i-dont-enjoy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2012 18:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/saturday-time-to-do-stuff-i-dont-enjoy/</guid>
      <description>Started the day off by cleaning up the Jmainguy.com site, noticed the A records for mc.jmainguy.com wasn’t correct. After some research saw that I had two A records, removed the bogus records and it should resolve correctly in a few hours. Also noticed the nsd3 server wasnt running for ns3.vpsaddict.com so I restarted that. ran update-rc.d nsd3 defaults to make sure its being loaded up at boot.
Browsed Reddit for a bit to pass the time, watched the rest of Wilfred on Netflix, watched some college football, so far no good games on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jon’s Monday night</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/jons-monday-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 02:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/jons-monday-night/</guid>
      <description>The Hall of Fame NFL game was this past weekend, and I missed it (Was helping a buddy move). So tonight I had to do 2 things before I could relax after a hard day.
Configure OpenVPN on my German node so I can browse the internet as your average German would.
Buy the Euro NFL Game Pass online streaming package so I can watch my Dolphins all year (Superbowl for sure this year).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jon cooks a meal</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/jon-cooks-a-meal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2012 18:23:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/jon-cooks-a-meal/</guid>
      <description>Today for lunch I decided I wanted Grilled Cheese and Tomato soup with Goldfish. There are a few issues with this decision.
Leah does not like melted cheese on bread, and refuses to make it for me.
We dont have tomoto soup or goldfish
I either buy or have Leah make my food.
However despite these obstacles I had my dream meal today. I went to the store and purchased the materials, and them made the meal myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setlist 2.0</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/setlist-2-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2012 00:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/setlist-2-0/</guid>
      <description>Now with HTML5 instead of googles audio player which they appear to have taken offline.
https://jmainguy.com/setlist</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Success at work yesterday</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/success-at-work-yesterday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2012 14:18:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/success-at-work-yesterday/</guid>
      <description>The web team asked me to help out on two projects yesterday, it was a ton of fun. The first project was to a 301 redirect working for the Iowa Hawkshop, they needed this to preserve their SEO ranking.
I was able to figure out we could use the Apache mod_rewrite to handle these requests.
The second task was to get rotating images on a timer with alt text via javascript.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Church Picnic</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/church-picnic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2012 17:46:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/church-picnic/</guid>
      <description>Church had a picnic last night, ended up heading out there around 6pm. We setup the lawn chairs we bought for the last picnic and settled in for a good time. There was a local band playing on the acoustic guitar and congo, cute kids and puppies running around, and good ol fashion corn hole. I ended up getting a few in the hole but our team lost pretty bad. Ate 2 chili dogs and some potato salad, topped off with a few chips a hoy cookies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WURM!!!</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/wurm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 18:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/wurm/</guid>
      <description>Started playing Wurm again the other day, I enjoy it quite a bit and hopefully don’t get burned out again.
Day 1. Spent the day replanting my crops, mining rocks from the mine, turning said rocks into bricks, using said bricks to repair house and fences. After that I went adventuring and found a Champion Dog, a Champion Cave Bug, a Slow Deer, a Raging Deer, a Sly Dog, a Hardened Dog, and 3-4 Scared Unicorns, which I tamed and brought back home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Todays Lunch</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/todays-lunch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 17:50:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/todays-lunch/</guid>
      <description>Went to a Italian place for lunch today, got the Sausage and Peppers panini, it was delicious, after the meal we all noticed the ceiling fan directly above our table.
Dust bunny anyone?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Away on Business</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/away-on-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2012 15:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/away-on-business/</guid>
      <description>Sorry for not updating this at all since before January, life has been going well, I am now drumming for my local church, and this week Sequoia sent me on a install trip to Savannah Georgia. Savannah is very fun and I took a few pictures.
Local game shop had this rare item in the window, the Nintendo Power Glove.
&amp;ldquo;Behold the Power&amp;rdquo;
My Hotel room
View from Hotel window.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goals for Jan</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/goals-for-jan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2012 13:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/goals-for-jan/</guid>
      <description>(1:40:16 PM) Adrian Thomas: Your targets this month are 9 resolutions daily
(1:40:39 PM) Adrian Thomas: AVG days open for Jan 15. days or less
(1:41:08 PM) Adrian Thomas: And submit 4 KB articles to Vanessa. E-mail her and copy me on them</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas List</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/christmas-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2011 02:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/christmas-list/</guid>
      <description>touchstone I wouldnt pay more then $40 for this &amp;lt;a href=http://www.walmart.com/ip/HP-TouchPad-Touchstone-Charging-Dock-Stand/16641540?ci_sku=16641540&amp;amp;ci_src=14110944&amp;amp;sourceid=1500000000000003142050&amp;gt;Touchstone Link at Walmart
newegg.com giftcards Newegg.com
RHCSA/RHCE Red Hat Linux Certification Study Guide (Exams EX200 &amp;amp; EX300), 6th Edition (Certification Press) by Michael Jang Paperback Amazon Link</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where did you sleep last night</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/where-did-you-sleep-last-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2011 06:44:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/where-did-you-sleep-last-night/</guid>
      <description>Fascinated with this song right now.
Black girl, black girl, don’t lie to me, tell me where did you sleep last night. In the pines, in the pines, where the sun dont ever shine, I would shiver the whole night through.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setlist</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/preparing-for-the-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 00:38:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/preparing-for-the-show/</guid>
      <description>Stuff I am currently practicing Setlist</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NC Drivers License Written Test</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/nc-drivers-license-written-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2011 05:47:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/nc-drivers-license-written-test/</guid>
      <description>In densely packed snow you should…use chains or snow tires.
If you must drive during heavy snow or fog, use your… low-beam headlights.
Alcohol-related highway deaths account for… 38% of all traffic fatalities.
If you accumulate 7 or more points on your traffic record you may… attend a Driver Improvement Clinic to deduct three points from your driving record.
The traffic conviction that adds the highest number of points (5) to your driving record is… passing a stopped school bus that is loading or unloading children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 14:09:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/facebook/</guid>
      <description>Removed all my friends, I do not intend on using Facebook anymore, it was fun for college but seems pretty pointless now, if people care about me they know me in real life and wont need Facebook to contact me. If you want to know my latest status I will start posting it here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Job, New Town, I love it</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/new-job-new-town-i-love-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2011 16:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/new-job-new-town-i-love-it/</guid>
      <description>Two months since last post, alot has been going on. Within a week of moving to Garner I received a job at a company that acted as middle men for AT&amp;amp;T Cellular tower installations, it was really quite neat but the job was basically data entry and run by people (very very nice people who I enjoyed working with) who had never done data entry so they had no idea what to expect us to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello North Carolina</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/hello-north-carolina/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2011 14:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/hello-north-carolina/</guid>
      <description>It has been a week since we moved to Garner and it has been a great week, the weather is awesome, the apartment is awesome, all the shops within 5 minutes of us is awesome, and it has been great to hang out with my cousins and their family. I also landed a contract job that I will start on Tuesday. So far everything has been going great and it looks like the move was a good idea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye Maryland</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/goodbye-maryland/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2011 20:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/goodbye-maryland/</guid>
      <description>Tomorrow will be my last day as an Employed individual, and Saturday will be my last day as a Maryland resident. I am North Carolina bound, the wife and I will be moving to Garner NC to save up some money, we hope to buy a house within the next two years. I will also pursue my dream of a full time career in the Information Technology field. I also might start a VPS reseller business, but I am not sure atm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/vacation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 14:49:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/vacation/</guid>
      <description>Ft Lauderdale is awesome, we are having a blast. So far we haven’t done much other then visit family but thats what we like to do. It really is a pleasure to be able to relax and not worry about anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Change of Scenery</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/change-of-scenery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 19:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/change-of-scenery/</guid>
      <description>Going to Ft. Lauderdale for a 5 day weekend starting tomorrow night, really looking forward to seeing all my family down there, and then starting in March I will be seeing alot more of that side of the family as well, stay tuned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CompTIA A&#43; Certified</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/comptia-a-certified/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2010 18:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/comptia-a-certified/</guid>
      <description>After studying on my own for a few months and utilizing the Mike Meyers A+ book, I took and passed both A+ tests this weekend. This was a huge relief as the A+ rules are changing again in about 2 weeks. Needless to say I am very happy right now =)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another new VPS</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/another-new-vps/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 23:25:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/another-new-vps/</guid>
      <description>the minecraft servers with hazenet didnt turn out the way I liked them, so I have moved them to 123systems which is located in Texas along, the babo servers will stay with hazenet also in texas. mmmm texas</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Babo Donors</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/babo-donors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2010 06:25:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/babo-donors/</guid>
      <description>In a span of 3 days after asking for donations, the babo players donated $110.00 or in other words, enough to rent a Virtual private server for 12 months. The server is awesome and way better then when hosted on my crappy home comcast connection. Babo Players Rule</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minecraft Players Rule</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/minecraft-players-rule/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2010 14:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/minecraft-players-rule/</guid>
      <description>So I have been spending alot of time on the Minecraft server lately, got a google maps image of the server to update every night, Implemented a currency system into the server. And two more people have generoussly donated to buying a new physical server. I think I will save the donations up for a 6 core computer I know I can build for $500.00 however by the time I get to that mark I am sure it will be even more beast then that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whole week no blog?</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/whole-week-no-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2010 17:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/whole-week-no-blog/</guid>
      <description>Sorry about that, Worked on server admin stuff all week, went over my bandwith cap by about 50gb, comcast will prolly send me a letter saying so. Working on automating server restart and backups, also working on php secure login page for the website and then hosting guest accounts for minecraft. Also playing NCAA 11 on my ps3 a little more, figured out a play that works and I run it non stop, still much harder game then NCAA 09.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Somebody has a case of the mondays</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/somebody-has-a-case-of-the-mondays/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2010 14:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/somebody-has-a-case-of-the-mondays/</guid>
      <description>Weekend went pretty well, saw the folks, went to a party, and Notch broke Minecraft again, however he has it working today so my server regulars should be happy. I also installed Sockso on the server so I can stream my music to any browser / operating system I want. Listening to my home collection at work is pretty fun. if any Mainguys would like to listen to my collection let me know and I will make you an account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Registered Sex Offender</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/registered-sex-offender/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2010 16:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/registered-sex-offender/</guid>
      <description>As usual watching Netflix and I was cruising the Indie section as sometimes they have a good gem in there, I came across RSO and decided to give it a shot. This movie is a Mockumentary and starts off interviewing the main character who is a sex offender. He is almost like-able in the beginning interview and seems like a normalish person, however throughout the rest of the movie you could care less about him and your waiting for the point of the movie where he will make a change for the better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remote Support</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/remote-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 14:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/remote-support/</guid>
      <description>I have installed a new remote support app on the website, all users have to do is download the program and run it. when the service is over the program deletes itself. pretty cool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minecraft Donation</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/minecraft-donation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2010 16:43:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/minecraft-donation/</guid>
      <description>About two days ago I asked the people who frequent my servers if they could donate a small amount so I could buy a Minecraft account and not have to borrow from Titans. To my surprise within one hour I had three donations that totaled exactly what I needed, Thank you very much to the people who donated. C Jaworski-Leeuwis, Niki ch, and Cynthia Stickle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Griefers</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/griefers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2010 04:11:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/griefers/</guid>
      <description>Wiped the minecraft server tonight, just way to much griefing to fix, easier to start over. Also Boise State upset VA Tech in football, awesome game. Labor day weekend went pretty well, dad was a little irked but overall a good time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forum was easy</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/forum-was-easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2010 20:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/forum-was-easy/</guid>
      <description>Ok so the forum was actually ridiculously easy to set up after all, downloaded the software, followed the installation guide, then placed the folders inside the index Apache looks at. it loaded right up and I could finish the install from the Easton computer. pretty cool stuff, now if only the Email server would be that easy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Labor Day weekend</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/labor-day-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2010 17:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/labor-day-weekend/</guid>
      <description>At the folks house on the eastern shore for the weekend, I am in the middle of my needed maintence on their home computer as the kids have loaded it up full of bad programs and such, defragging it as it looks like a solid red bar. Also today I will attempt to install a forum for the website as the people who play my minecraft server have requested one. as usual it isnt as easy as it should be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minecraft</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/minecraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2010 02:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/minecraft/</guid>
      <description>Starting hosting a Minecraft server and playing on Titans account, its alot of fun and very addicting, I wasted alot of time on it today and the day before. I really enjoy building thins in the game, and directing the flow of water or lava. as usual if you want to play connect to my server by typing this in command console. “ping jmainguy.com” then use the ip you get from that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bad mood</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/bad-mood/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2010 17:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/bad-mood/</guid>
      <description>Its just on of those days, where you dont want to wake up, everything is fucked, everybody sucks. You dont really know why, but you want to justify, ripping someones head off. I am Eeyore</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Babo Weekend</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/babo-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2010 14:46:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/babo-weekend/</guid>
      <description>Friday night a little after 6 the rndlabs.ca servers for baboviolent 2 went down, and they haven’t come back up yet. this is the longest period of time that they have been done in the last three years. Over its history the servers where first provided by the creators dZb and Daivuk, then when they didnt want to pay for servers for a free game Vamp stepped up and paid for about a year, then Deathray took over when Vamp got sick of doing it, and now?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fed Up</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/fed-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 16:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/fed-up/</guid>
      <description>In the last 30 days I have spent $1,433.19 on stuff other then rent, 24 percent on grocerys, 19 perent on games and movies, 16 percent on gasoline, 12 percent on fast food, and 22 percent on phone bill (we got new phones). hopefully next month we will do better, I think I will try and set a budget and see how we do. The current budget being if we have cash, spend it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website Headaches</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/website-headaches/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2010 13:21:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/website-headaches/</guid>
      <description>Well I am proud that I have gotten this far, I have completed a Home page, a page dedicated to babo, and now this blog. However I still have a ways to go, I need to get the email server up and running which is proving to be a major headache, I also need to adjust this blog to resemble the rest of the website, as of right now it looks entirely different and impossible to get back to the main page of the website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>obert-</title>
      <link>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/obert/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 23:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jmainguy.com/index.php/obert/</guid>
      <description>This website was built with the help of many individuals who took the time to explain to me my errors and how to fix them, one of them “obert-” from the #wordpress channel on the freenode server; took time to help me setup this blog page and I want to personally thank him for his efforts. Thank you obert</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
